
// mongoimport --uri mongodb://Dev:Dev1987@ds115022.mlab.com:15022/spaced-rep --collection questions --file DB/seed-questions.json --jsonArray

[
  {
  "question": "Car",
  "answer": "Carro",
  "numCorrect": 0,
  "numAttempts": 0
  },
  {
  "question": "Cat",
  "answer": "Gato",
  "numCorrect": 0,
  "numAttempts": 0
  },
  {
  "question": "Dog",
  "answer": "Perro",
  "numCorrect": 0,
  "numAttempts": 0
  },
  {
  "question": "Bush",
  "answer": "Arbusto",
  "numCorrect": 0,
  "numAttempts": 0
  },
  {
  "question": "Tree",
  "answer": "Arbol",
  "numCorrect": 0,
  "numAttempts": 0
  },
  {
  "question": "Water",
  "answer": "Agua",
  "numCorrect": 0,
  "numAttempts": 0
  },
  {
  "question": "Sky",
  "answer": "Cielo",
  "numCorrect": 0,
  "numAttempts": 0
  },
  {
  "question": "Cloud",
  "answer": "Nube",
  "numCorrect": 0,
  "numAttempts": 0
  },
  {
  "question": "Fire",
  "answer": "Fuego",
  "numCorrect": 0,
  "numAttempts": 0
  },
  {
  "question": "Wind",
  "answer": "Viento",
  "numCorrect": 0,
  "numAttempts": 0
  }
  
]